A Guide to the Records of the Clan MacLeod Society USA, 1899-2009
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Events 1951-2007.
  - Games
    - Central Virginia Scottish Festival and Games at Scotchtown (Box-folder 97:15)
    - Annual Charleston Scottish Games and Highland Gathering (Box-folder 97:16)
    - 15th Annual Colonial Highland Gathering, Fair Hill, Maryland June 5, 1976 (Box-folder 97:17)
    - Flora MacDonald Highland Games, Red Springs, North Carolina (Box-folder 97:18)
    - Glasgow Kentucky Highland Games and Parade (Box-folder 97:19)
    - Grandfather Mountain Games, North Carolina (I) (Box-folder 97:20)
    - Grandfather Mountain Games, North Carolina (II) (Box-folder 97:21)
    - Highland Games and Scottish Events (flyer) 1978 (Box-folder 97:22)
    - Highlands and Islands Associations of Celtic Gatherings Inc., Annual Scottish Games and Celtic Festival on the Gulf Coast (Box-folder 97:23)
    - 1st Annual Jacksonville Scottish Highland Games February 17, 1996 (Box-folder 97:24)
    - 32nd Annual Ligonier Highland Games 1990 (Box-folder 97:25)
    - Loch Norman Highland Games (Box-folder 97:26)
    - Macalester College Scottish Country Fair Highland Games, St. Paul Minnesota 1989 (Box-folder 97:27)
    - Orlando Scottish Highland Games and Gathering of the Clans 1989 (Box-folder 97:28)
    - Rio Grande Valley Celtic Festival and Games (Box-folder 97:29)
    - Annual Savannah Scottish Games and Highland Gathering (Box-folder 97:30)
    - Southeast Florida Scottish Festival and Games (Box-folder 97:31)
    - Stone Mountain Highland Games (Box-folder 97:32)
    - Tennessee Valley: North Alabama Scottish Festival 1992 (Box-folder 97:33)
    - 4th Annual Texas Scottish Festival and Highland Games 1990 (Box-folder 97:34)
    - Tidewater Festival (Box-folder 97:35)
    - Virginia Scottish Games (Box-folder 97:36)
    - Waxhaw Scottish Games and Gathering of the Clans, Waxhaw, North Carolina (Box-folder 97:37)
    - Williamsburg Virginia Scottish Festival (Box-folder 97:38)
    - Miscellaneous games and events (Box-folder 97:39)
    - Glennfiddich Games poster May 14-15, 1983 (Box Oversize Box 1)
    - Grandfather Mountain-Highland Games and Gathering of Scottish Clans-flyers 1950s-1960s (Box Oversize Box 2)
  - Visits
    - Associated Clan MacLeod Societies accommodation scheme February 22, 1973 (Box-folder 98:1)
    - Invitation to New York, Central Atlantic, and New England MacLeods to visit Maybelle MacLeod Luman at her estate Dunvegan in Crozet Virginia March 28, 1964 (Box-folder 98:2)
    - Alice MacNab 1975 (Box-folder 98:3)
    - Dr. George F. MacLeod of Iona 1970s? (Box-folder 98:4)
    - Chief John and Melita's visit to Princeton, New Jersey 1977 (Box-folder 98:5)
    - Chief John and Melita's Chief John and Melita's visit to the Carolinas March 1980 (Box-folder 98:6)
    - The Magical Misty Tour: report of U.S. visit of Norman of Suardal and his wife Sheila, written by Neil Stewart MacLeod March 1987 (Box-folder 98:7)
    - Torquil Roderick of the MacLeods of Lewes and wife Mary: tour of the U.S.A. July-August 1989 (Box-folder 98:8)
    - Angus and Julia's visit to America 1991 (Box-folder 98:9)
    - Chief John's visit to South Africa 2004 (Box-folder 98:10)
    - Chief Hugh MacLeod's visit to New York City 2007 (Box-folder 98:11)
  - Visits-Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod
    - Canada visit 1951 (Box-folder 98:12)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod U.S. visit with twin grandsons 1953 (Box-folder 98:13)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod, Canadian trip 1955-56 (Box-folder 98:14)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod U.S. visit 1955-56 (Box-folder 98:15)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod U.S. visit 1957 (Box-folder 98:16)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod U.S. visit 1958 (Box-folder 98:17)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod U.S. visit 1961 (Box-folder 98:18)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod U.S. visit 1962 (Box-folder 98:19)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod U.S. visit 1964 (Box-folder 98:20)
    - Announcement of upcoming visit by Chief Flora January 1965 (Box-folder 98:21)
    - Draft of itinerary for Dame Flora and Joan Wolridge Gordon's visit 1969? (Box-folder 98:22)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod: visits to Washington D.C. 1968-1972 (Box-folder 98:23)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (Box-folder 98:24)
  - Queen's Visit to Dunvegan
    - Clippings (Box-folder 98:25)
  - Workshops
    - Clan MacLeod historical seminars 1986, 1994 (Box-folder 98:26)
  - Miscellaneous events: United States
    - Clan MacLeod Society gathering: Millis, Massachusetts December 9, 1955 (Box-folder 98:27)
    - Clan MacLeod Society gathering: Jacksonville, Florida March 2, 1957 (Box-folder 98:28)
    - Funeral program for Angus MacLeod and article May 1958 (Box-folder 98:29)
    - Scottish Nationality Day at the New York's World Fair August 16, 1964 (Box-folder 98:30)
    - Clan MacLeod Society gathering October 7, 1967 (Box-folder 98:31)
    - Funeral program for Marietta McLeod and clippings regarding her death December 21, 1972 (Box-folder 98:32)
    - Bay-Area gathering for the MacLeods November 15, 1980 (Box-folder 99:1)
    - Christmas Walk, Alexandria VA 1980-82, 1990 (Box-folder 99:2)
    - Informal Celidh, Arlington, Massachusetts May 1981 (Box-folder 99:3)
    - Two Big Events May 1982 (Box-folder 99:4)
    - Memorial service for Maybelle Luman September 25, 1982 (Box-folder 99:5)
    - In Honor of Daniel R. MacLeod: South Carolina Attorney General, 1959-1983, Carolina Coliseum, Columbia, South Carolina January 6, 1983 (Box-folder 99:6)
    - Clan MacLeod-Carolinas party September 17, 1983 (Box-folder 99:7)
    - MacLeod-MacDonald Celidh in Lumberton North Carolina October 5, 1985 (Box-folder 99:8)
    - Memorial service for Virginia L. MacLeod November 14, 1985 (Box-folder 99:9)
    - 1st Annual Highland Fling Weekend and 12th Annual Burns Dinner, Robert Burns Society of the Midlands, Columbia, South Carolina January 20, 1990 (Box-folder 99:10)
    - 5th Annual gathering of the Clans and Queen Victoria Birthday Celebration Fort Vancouver, Washington May 20, 1990 (Box-folder 99:11)
    - Clan MacLeod Society of Southern California, 9th Annual Skye Ball October 13, 1990 (Box-folder 99:12)
    - Skye Celidh-Clan MacLeod Society Metropolitan Chapter, Chevy Chase Country Club, Glendale California October 12, 1991 (Box-folder 99:13)
    - Spring in the Highlands of Watertown, Massachusetts May 15, 1994 (Box-folder 99:14)
    - Kirkin O' the Tartan: Independent Presbyterian Church, Savannah Georgia May 14, 1995 (Box-folder 99:15)
    - The Amazing Gathering of the MacLeods, Braintree, Massachusetts July 20-23, 1995 (Box-folder 99:16)
    - Doug MacLeod's 75th Birthday January 20, 1996 (Box-folder 99:17)
    - Scottish Heritage Celebration: Laurinburg, Lumberton, and Red Springs North Carolina 1996 (Box-folder 99:18)
    - To a Life Well Lived-A service in memory of Charles Anderson McLeod: 1916-1998 (Box-folder 99:19)
    - Obituary/funeral: Frances E. Pearson July 28, 2000 (Box-folder 99:20)
    - Tartan Day Parade, New York City 2007 (Box-folder 99:21)
    - Coming Events Schedule, undated (Box-folder 99:22)
    - Colonial Cup Gathering, South Carolina, undated (Box-folder 99:23)
    - MacLeod Day, Harnett County Centennial, undated (Box-folder 99:24)
    - Proclamation of Clan MacLeod Week in Decatur, Georgia April 19, 1990 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous events: Scotland and Elsewhere
    - Invitation to the wedding of Anne Howard to Patrick Wolridge Gordon 1962? (Box-folder 99:25)
    - Tour of Isles of Lewis and Harris August 3-6, 1974 (Box-folder 99:26)
    - Laura Margaret MacLeod's visit to Nova Scotia and Toronto Summer 1984 (Box-folder 99:27)
    - Clan MacLeod Society of Scotland Centenary Weekend September 19-22, 1991 (Box-folder 99:28)
    - The Iona Community: A service of thanksgiving and recommitment in gratitude for the life of George Fielden MacLeod September 21, 1991 (Box-folder 99:29)
    - Dunvegan Castle 12th Arts Festival July, 1992 (Box-folder 99:30)
    - The Grand MacLeod Reunion in Ireland 1993 (Box-folder 99:31)
    - Grand Reunion in Scotland 1994 (Box-folder 99:32)
    - Alexander McLeod's European trip 1998 (Box-folder 99:33)
    - Clan MacLeod Society of England: dinner at the House of Lords July 30, 1998 (Box-folder 99:34)
    - Clan MacLeod [Society] of England: annual dinners 2001 and 2001 (Box-folder 99:35)
    - Associated Clan MacLeod Societies 40th birthday weekend January-February 2001 (Box-folder 99:36)
    - New Zealand Gathering 2003 (Box-folder 99:37)
    - Service of thanksgiving and celebration of Norman MacLeod of Suardal, 1920-2005 (Box-folder 99:38)
    - North Idaho College, Scotland study and tour, undated (Box-folder 99:39)
- Photographs 1899-2006.
  This series contains photographs relating to the events, places, and members of Clan MacLeod. The series is divided into eight sub-series. Sub-series A: Annual General Meeting; Sub-series B: Dunvegan Castle; Sub-series C: Events; Sub-series D: Parliament; Sub-series E: Portraits; Sub-series F: Portraits-Dame Flora; Sub-series G: Unknown Events; Sub-series H: Miscellaneous. This series is arranged in chronological and alphabetical order.
  - Annual General Meeting
    - Annual banquet January 1957 (Box-folder 100:1)
    - Annual banquet January 1958 (Box-folder 100:2)
    - Annual general meeting and banquet photos, undated 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 100:3)
    - Joan Wolridge Gordon, Norman W. MacLeod, and Donald B. MacLeod February 1965 (Box-folder 100:4)
    - Annual general meeting dinner with Patrick and Anne Wolridge Gordon, Joan Wolridge Gordon and Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod 1970 (Box-folder 100:5)
    - Debutantes presented at Annual General Meeting 1970 (Box-folder 100:6)
    - Annual general meeting: Nashville, Tennessee 1975 (Box-folder 100:7)
    - Annual general meeting: Princeton, New Jersey 1978 (Box-folder 100:8)
    - Miscellaneous annual general meeting photos 1970s? (Box-folder 100:9)
    - Miscellaneous annual general meeting photos 1980s? (Box-folder 100:10)
    - Oversize photo of the Skye Association of New York, 26th annual Dinner in honor of Dr. Herbert MacLeod, Building Trades Club (includes letter from April 10, 1990 giving descriptive information about the photo) February 12, 1937 (Box Oversize Box 2)
    - Oversize photo of the 13th Annual Dinner of the Clan MacLeod Society of America, Waldorf-Astoria, New York City February 4, 1967 (Box Oversize Box 2)
    - Oversize photo of the 15th Annual Dinner of the Clan MacLeod Society of America, Waldorf-Astoria, New York City February 4, 1969 (Box Oversize Box 2)
  - Dunvegan Castle
    - Photos of Dunvegan Castle: exterior (Box-folder 100:11)
    - Interior: dining room with Dame Flora's portrait and unidentified visitors. Staff photo by Tom Rogers of the Tennessean (Box-folder 100:12)
    - B/W and color photos of the castle at sunset, undated (Box-folder 100:13)
    - Negatives of Dunvegan Castle and grounds (Box-folder 100:14)
    - Paintings of Dunvegan Castle and grounds (Box-folder 100:15)
    - Exterior photo of Dunvegan Castle with sheep in foreground (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Events
    - Dame Flora's arrival in New York 1953 (Box-folder 101:1)
    - John and Patrick Wolridge Gordon's arrival in New York on their first visit to the U.S.A. (Box-folder 101:2)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod and Dr. Louis LaMotte, president of Presbyterian Junior College, Maxton, North Carolina. (Box-folder 101:3)
    - Dame Flora speaking at Fayetteville MacLeod Clan Meeting(group photo in multiple parts) September 28, 1953 (Box-folder 101:4)
    - Dame Flora's visits to the United States, 1950s (Box-folder 101:5)
    - Organizing committee: Chicago, Illinois February 19-20, 1954 (Box-folder 101:6)
    - Clan MacLeod Society of U.S.A.'s wedding gift to John and Drusilla 1961 (Box-folder 101:7)
    - Dame Flora and Seton Gordon talking at Boreraig Day, undated (Box-folder 101:8)
    - Photo slides of Dame Flora's funeral 1976 (Box-folder 101:9)
    - Clan and society leaders at Grandfather Mountain Games (includes Purdy MacLeod) July 1983 (Box-folder 101:10)
    - Chief Torquil Roderick's visit to the United States 1989 (Box-folder 101:11)
    - Dunvegan Foundation Workshop, Nashville Tennessee April 4, 1992 (Box-folder 101:12)
    - Presentation to Alexander C. MacLeod, M.D., F.S.A. with a rendition of the Associated Clan MacLeod Societies arms 1994 (Box-folder 101:13)
    - Associated Clan MacLeod Societies meeting in Bendigo, Australia May 1999 (Box-folder 101:14)
    - Genealogist Jim Hunter's visit to North Carolina 2000s (Box-folder 101:15)
    - New Zealand gathering group photo 2003 (Box-folder 101:16)
    - 50th anniversary dinner group photo 2004 (Box-folder 101:17)
    - North American gathering in Chicago, group photo 2004 (Box-folder 101:18)
    - Chicago Gathering photos 2004 (Box-folder 101:19)
    - Suradal House renovation project 2004 (Box-folder 101:20)
  - Parliament
    - Parliament group photo 1956 (Box-folder 102:1)
    - Parliament: members departing to Scotland 1956 (Box-folder 102:2)
    - Parliament group photo 1968 (Box-folder 102:3)
    - Undated Parliament photos 1960s? (Box-folder 102:4)
    - Parliament group photo 1971 (Box-folder 102:5)
    - Parliament photos? 1998 (Box-folder 102:6)
    - Parliament group photo 2002 (Box-folder 102:7)
    - Parliament group photo 2006 (Box-folder 102:8)
  - Portraits
    - Murray, Nancy, Kristine Anderson 1970s? (Box-folder 103:1)
    - Joan Wolridge Gordon and Marietta MacLeod 1960s (Box-folder 103:2)
    - Mary MacLeod Layton 1963 (Box-folder 103:3)
    - Anne MacLeod, Bruce MacLeod 1980s, 1990s, 2000s (Box-folder 103:4)
    - Brenda MacLeod 1938-39? (Box-folder 103:5)
    - John A. MacLeod and family 1800s-1900s (Box-folder 103:6)
    - John MacLeod of MacLeod 1950s, 1970s (Box-folder 103:7)
    - Laura Margaret MacLeod 1950s, 1960s, 1980s (Box-folder 103:8)
    - Marietta MacLeod and family 1950s (Box-folder 103:9)
    - Maud MacLeod and family 1970s-80s (Box-folder 103:10)
    - Murdo MacLeod and family 1999 (Box-folder 103:11)
    - Neil MacLeod and family 1990s? (Box-folder 103:12)
    - J. Norman MacLeod 1976-77 (Box-folder 103:13)
    - Sir Reginald MacLeod of MacLeod (Box-folder 104:1)
    - Robert(Bob)MacLeod (Box-folder 104:2)
    - Virginia MacLeod and Frances Pearson (Box-folder 104:3)
    - Ralph and Robin March (Box-folder 104:4)
    - Dr. Alexander C. McLeod and family 1980s-90s (Box-folder 104:5)
    - Dick and Barbara McLeod 1990s (Box-folder 104:6)
    - Miscellaneous MacLeod portraits (Box-folder 104:7)
    - Miscellaneous portrait negatives (Box-folder 104:8)
  - Portraits-Dame Flora
    - Photo of painted portrait of Dame Flora by W.O. Hutchinson 1952 (Box-folder 104:9)
    - Portrait at entrance to Dunvegan Castle through the sea-gate, British Travel Association photo 1953 (Box-folder 104:10)
    - Magazine photo of Dame Flora in front of Dunvegan Castle, from Society Magazine 1970 (Box-folder 104:11)
    - As Dame Flora enters her 100th year on February 3rd: photo by Tom Rogers of the Tennessean 1975 (Box-folder 104:12)
    - Remembrance photo of Dame Flora (Box-folder 104:13)
    - Negative of Dame Flora on Dunvegan grounds (Box-folder 104:14)
    - Photo of painted portrait of Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod by W.O. Hutchinson, signed Laura Margaret from Flora MacLeod of MacLeod, Hold Fast by Dame Flora 1952 (Box Oversize Box 1)
    - Portrait by Elizabeth M. Layton 1955 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Unknown Events
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod and unidentified group 1940s-1950s? (Box-folder 105:1)
    - Maryland/Washington D.C. gathering 1980s? (Box-folder 105:2)
    - Clan MacLeod of Germany gathering? (Box-folder 105:3)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Clan MacLeod Dancers (Box-folder 105:4)
    - ODU Archives photos (Box-folder 105:5)
    - Photo of the official arms of the Associated Clan MacLeod Societies (Box-folder 105:6)
    - Scotland photos (Box-folder 105:7)
    - West Virginia Highlanders Legion Pipe Band, various events 1987-88 (Box-folder 105:8)
    - Miscellaneous photos (Box-folder 105:9)
    - Negative of Murdoch McLeod crest (Box-folder 105:10)
    - Slide and negatives of Clan Crest (Box-folder 105:11)
- Electronic Media 1970-2006.
  This series contains various media relating to the documents and events of Clan MacLeod. Various media consists of reel to reel audio tapes, audiocassettes, computer diskettes, documentation of digital files, web page printouts, video, film, and microfiche. There are five sub-series. Sub-series A: Audiocassettes/Reels; Sub-series B: Computer Files; Sub-series C: Website; Sub-series D: Film and Video; Sub-series E: Microfiche. This series is arranged in chronological order by type of media.
  - Audiocassettes/Reels
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day one 1971 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day two 1971 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day three (I) 1971 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day three (II) 1971 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day one (I) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day one (II) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day one (III) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day two 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day three(I) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, day three (II) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, final day (I) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, final day (II) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio reel to reel tape: Parliament, final day (III) 1974 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio cassette: The Very Reverend Lord George MacLeod of Fiunary Kirkin of [the] Tartan, Washington, D.C. 1972 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio cassette: Alice Morrison, genealogy address, 9th Parliament 1978 (Box Box 106)
    - Audio cassette: (Side A) Angus MacLeod, (Side B) Harry Boyes (Box Box 106)
    - Audio cassette: (Side A) Meeting Council, (Side B) Treasurer Audit (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Parliament 1990 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Scotland 1990 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting 1991 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Closing of Annual General Meeting 1991? (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting 1992 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Meeting with Alexander McLeod 1992 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Council 1992 with Alexander McLeod (I) 1992 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Council 1992 with Alexander McLeod (II) 1992 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Council 1992 with Alexander McLeod (III) 1992 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Council 1992 with Alexander McLeod (IV) 1992 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Council 1992 with Alexander McLeod (V) 1992 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Associated Clan MacLeod Societies (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting with Alexander McLeod 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting and Council Meeting (I) 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting and Council Meeting (II) 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting and Council Meeting (III) 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting and Council Meeting (IV) 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting and Council Meeting (V) 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting and Council Meeting (VI) 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Annual General Meeting and Council Meeting (VII) 1993 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: answering machine message April 28, 1991 (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Contents unknown (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Contents unknown (Box Box 106)
    - Mini audio cassette: Contents unknown (Box Box 106)
  - Computer Files
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-1 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-2 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-3 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-4 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-5 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-6 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-7 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-8 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-9 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-10 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-11 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-12 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-13 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-14 (Box Box 107)
    - 1.44 MB formatted floppy diskette labeled DF-15 (Box Box 107)
    - Index of materials stored on diskettes (Box-folder 107:1)
    - Clan CD-ROM information (Box-folder 107:2)
    - Correspondence regarding data files (Box-folder 107:3)
    - Sample computer record (Box-folder 107:4)
    - Symmetrical data delivery on HFC systems by Bruce MacLeod (Box-folder 107:5)
    - Diskette: photos of Uignish House (unzipped) and accompanying document (Box-folder 107:6)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part one-notes August 1998-September 2006 (Box Box 108)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files 1998 (Box Box 108)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files 1999 (Box Box 108)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (1 of 2) 2000 (Box Box 108)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (2 of 2) 2000 (Box Box 109)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (1 of 2) 2001 (Box Box 109)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (2 of 2) 2001 (Box Box 109)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (1 of 2) 2002 (Box Box 109)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (2 of 2) 2002 (Box Box 110)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (1 of 2) 2003 (Box Box 110)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (2 of 2) 2003 (Box Box 110)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (1 of 2) 2004 (Box Box 111)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (2 of 2) 2004 (Box Box 111)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (1 of 3) 2005 (Box Box 111)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (2 of 3) 2005 (Box Box 112)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (3 of 3) 2005 (Box Box 112)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (1 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 112)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part two-primary files (2 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 113)